hello welcome to the course physics as
information processing taught by Chris
Fields with Andre Aguirre as a course
assistant hosted during 2023 by the
octave inference Institute this video is
an overview of the course website it's
going to cover some of the key pieces of
the website and ways to participate
the course homepage hosts the key links
and a written course overview
on the course syllabus page
there's a table with each row being one
session so here you can see the topic
and the preparation for each of the six
lectures and you can see information
about the six discussion sections which
will be following each lecture by about
two weeks
each lecture and discussion you can
click this blue icon and go directly to
the video to re-watch it or watch it
live or you can go to the playlist to
watch all videos sequentially
so that's one way that you can
participate is watching videos live or
re-watching them
on the questions and answers page
there's a form that you can submit you
can say what is time
and if you submit that question we'll
get it on the back end and Chris Fields
will answer the question and then the
question and answer will come up to the
public front end and along with the
transcripts of all sessions these
questions and answers will be part of
the publication that we prepare at the
end of the course so we heartily
encourage all questions and answers it's
a really easy and important Anonymous
way for you to contribute
lastly you can go to register to join
discussions so if you want to join those
live interactive discussion live streams
about two weeks after each lecture you
can complete this form and we'll add you
to calendar events so
thanks again for your interest in the
course physics is information processing
and we hope to see you either watching
and re-watching the videos asking
questions and answers and maybe even
registering to join the discussions
thanks and see you there